Chandler Love

Munich, Germany •+49 176 54601273 •clove20123@gmail.com

Potfolio ◆LinkedIn ◆Xing

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- React
- React Native
- JavaScript
- Non-Relational

Databases

Relational

Databases

- Node.js
- Angular
- TypeScript
- Bootstrap
- Express
- Visual Studio
- Microsoft

Office

- Git
- Unit Testing
- End-To-End

Testing

Integration

Testing

<u>Junior Full-Stack web developer</u> with a background in sales. Ability to produce well organized code. Experienced with crafting UI designs for websites. Able to create backend APIs with non-relational and relational databases. Fast learner with outstanding problem-solving skills. Focused on customer satisfaction and customer retention.

CURRENT WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

07/2021-Present

- Working for a local osteopathy practice to deploy a website for their business.
- o Used HTML and CSS to create a slick, modern, and easy to navigate website
- o Generated a website that works on multiple devices to accommodate all customers
- o Continually making improvements and updating the website to stay on top of trends
- Constantly in contact with the practice to hear user experiences with the website

PROJECTS

- Created a Pokedex App using JavaScript to display details fetched from an external API into a modal.
- Constructed a client-side (React) and server-side (API) to allow users to create an
 account and search for movies.
- Designed a chat app using React Native that allows users to chat, send pictures, and share location.
- o Made another client-side movie app using Angular and TypeScript.

EXPERIENCE

01/2016-06/2019

SENIOR SALES ACCOUNT MANAGER, CHARLOTTE MOTOR SPEEDWAY

- Managed a portfolio of over 1140 accounts and acted as the point of contact to handle any customer needs.
- Maintained a trusted advisor relationship with key accounts to better fulfill their needs.
- Trained junior staff members so they could better understand the software.
- $\circ\quad$ Supervised staff through the process from prospecting to closing.
- Analyzed customer behavior and experience in order to improve future business relationships with customers, ultimately driving sales growth.

05/2012-12/2015

JUNIOR SALES ACCOUNT MANAGER, CHARLOTTE MOTOR SPEEDWAY

- Assisted customers with purchases.
- Clarified customer inquiries, such as regarding event schedules & details, ticket and event pricing, payment plan options, ticket insurance and return policies.
- Diagnosed customer complaints to help resolve issues efficiently.

EDUCATION

02/2021-12/2021

FULL-STACK WEB DEVEOLPER, CARERRFOUNDRY

- Server-Side Programming & Node.is
- Client-Side Programming and React
- Testing in the Development Process
- Native App Development and React Native
- o Collaboration and Documentation

08/2010-12/2015

BACHOLER OF SCIENCE IN BUISNESS ADMINISTRATION, UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT CHARLOTTE

- o Major: Management Information Systems
- Minor: Operations & Supply Chain Management